{
  "apikey": "%PUT-YOUR-API-KEY-HERE%",
  "description": "This is simple calibration data used for testing purposes. Do not use it in production environment!",
  "copyright": "Copyright (C) 2238 by BanAN Technologies Inc.",
  "test-data": [
    {
      "question": "80 + 7",
      "answer": 87
    },
    {
      "question": "4 + 82",
      "answer": 86
    },
    {
      "question": "47 + 26",
      "answer": 73
    },
    {
      "question": "48 + 39",
      "answer": 87
    },
    {
      "question": "64 + 8",
      "answer": 72
    },
    {
      "question": "69 + 28",
      "answer": 97
    },
    {
      "question": "32 + 91",
      "answer": 123
    },
    {
      "question": "41 + 98",
      "answer": 139
    },
    {
      "question": "11 + 2",
      "answer": 13
    },
    {
      "question": "17 + 35",
      "answer": 52
    },
    {
      "question": "95 + 78",
      "answer": 173
    },
    {
      "question": "7 + 81",
      "answer": 88
    },
    {
      "question": "23 + 61",
      "answer": 84
    },
    {
      "question": "47 + 85",
      "answer": 132
    },
    {
      "question": "76 + 1",
      "answer": 77
    },
    {
      "question": "43 + 37",
      "answer": 80
    },
    {
      "question": "29 + 96",
      "answer": 125
    },
    {
      "question": "57 + 81",
      "answer": 138
    },
    {
      "question": "3 + 22",
      "answer": 25
    },
    {
      "question": "63 + 28",
      "answer": 91
    },
    {
      "question": "84 + 67",
      "answer": 151
    },
    {
      "question": "22 + 31",
      "answer": 53
    },
    {
      "question": "41 + 30",
      "answer": 71
    },
    {
      "question": "52 + 82",
      "answer": 134
    },
    {
      "question": "100 + 8",
      "answer": 108
    },
    {
      "question": "13 + 55",
      "answer": 68
    },
    {
      "question": "81 + 67",
      "answer": 148
    },
    {
      "question": "97 + 73",
      "answer": 170
    },
    {
      "question": "41 + 22",
      "answer": 63
    },
    {
      "question": "37 + 62",
      "answer": 99
    },
    {
      "question": "71 + 63",
      "answer": 134
    },
    {
      "question": "17 + 79",
      "answer": 96
    },
    {
      "question": "39 + 61",
      "answer": 100
    },
    {
      "question": "25 + 20",
      "answer": 45
    },
    {
      "question": "86 + 79",
      "answer": 165
    },
    {
      "question": "89 + 30",
      "answer": 119
    },
    {
      "question": "82 + 27",
      "answer": 109
    },
    {
      "question": "44 + 70",
      "answer": 114
    },
    {
      "question": "81 + 58",
      "answer": 139
    },
    {
      "question": "99 + 87",
      "answer": 186
    },
    {
      "question": "2 + 54",
      "answer": 56
    },
    {
      "question": "63 + 41",
      "answer": 104
    },
    {
      "question": "86 + 60",
      "answer": 146
    },
    {
      "question": "39 + 32",
      "answer": 71
    },
    {
      "question": "2 + 91",
      "answer": 93
    },
    {
      "question": "96 + 3",
      "answer": 99
    },
    {
      "question": "98 + 84",
      "answer": 182
    },
    {
      "question": "17 + 46",
      "answer": 63
    },
    {
      "question": "97 + 26",
      "answer": 123
    },
    {
      "question": "5 + 81",
      "answer": 86
    },
    {
      "question": "16 + 22",
      "answer": 38
    },
    {
      "question": "85 + 79",
      "answer": 164
    },
    {
      "question": "100 + 57",
      "answer": 157
    },
    {
      "question": "38 + 60",
      "answer": 98
    },
    {
      "question": "78 + 21",
      "answer": 99
    },
    {
      "question": "99 + 4",
      "answer": 103
    },
    {
      "question": "35 + 87",
      "answer": 122
    },
    {
      "question": "72 + 74",
      "answer": 146
    },
    {
      "question": "55 + 15",
      "answer": 70
    },
    {
      "question": "32 + 83",
      "answer": 115
    },
    {
      "question": "33 + 81",
      "answer": 114
    },
    {
      "question": "32 + 76",
      "answer": 108
    },
    {
      "question": "100 + 68",
      "answer": 168
    },
    {
      "question": "95 + 55",
      "answer": 150
    },
    {
      "question": "97 + 58",
      "answer": 155
    },
    {
      "question": "44 + 3",
      "answer": 47
    },
    {
      "question": "82 + 70",
      "answer": 152
    },
    {
      "question": "17 + 34",
      "answer": 51
    },
    {
      "question": "22 + 50",
      "answer": 72
    },
    {
      "question": "87 + 24",
      "answer": 111
    },
    {
      "question": "33 + 89",
      "answer": 122
    },
    {
      "question": "70 + 42",
      "answer": 112
    },
    {
      "question": "9 + 51",
      "answer": 60
    },
    {
      "question": "8 + 52",
      "answer": 60
    },
    {
      "question": "35 + 28",
      "answer": 63
    },
    {
      "question": "52 + 81",
      "answer": 133
    },
    {
      "question": "8 + 7",
      "answer": 15
    },
    {
      "question": "44 + 88",
      "answer": 132
    },
    {
      "question": "71 + 71",
      "answer": 142
    },
    {
      "question": "98 + 79",
      "answer": 177
    },
    {
      "question": "2 + 16",
      "answer": 18
    },
    {
      "question": "95 + 61",
      "answer": 156
    },
    {
      "question": "90 + 36",
      "answer": 126
    },
    {
      "question": "73 + 91",
      "answer": 164
    },
    {
      "question": "66 + 41",
      "answer": 107
    },
    {
      "question": "76 + 50",
      "answer": 126
    },
    {
      "question": "85 + 30",
      "answer": 115
    },
    {
      "question": "85 + 10",
      "answer": 95
    },
    {
      "question": "80 + 30",
      "answer": 110
    },
    {
      "question": "7 + 40",
      "answer": 47
    },
    {
      "question": "45 + 53",
      "answer": 98
    },
    {
      "question": "52 + 88",
      "answer": 140
    },
    {
      "question": "94 + 65",
      "answer": 159
    },
    {
      "question": "16 + 48",
      "answer": 64
    },
    {
      "question": "23 + 54",
      "answer": 77
    },
    {
      "question": "12 + 63",
      "answer": 75
    },
    {
      "question": "11 + 60",
      "answer": 71
    },
    {
      "question": "45 + 51",
      "answer": 96
    },
    {
      "question": "21 + 39",
      "answer": 60
    },
    {
      "question": "10 + 40",
      "answer": 50
    }
  ],
  "chunk": {
    "number": 15,
    "total": 22,
    "size": 100,
    "range": {
      "from": 1400,
      "to": 1500
    }
  }
}